Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sheet Music (Irish), 1817-1995, 191937
  - D, 336039
    - Danny Boy, 1913, 1941; 193064 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Darling Mother Mine, 1921; 193063 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Daughter of Rose of Tralee, The, 1953; 193062 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Daughter of Rosie O'Grady, The, 1918; 193061 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Day I Left Old Erin, The, 1916; 193060 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Dear Erin, 1810-12; 193059 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Dear Ireland, 1905; 193058 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Dear Ireland When You're Free, 1898; 193057 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Dear Irish Maiden I Loved Long Ago, The, 1901; 193056 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Dear Little Boy of Mine, 1918; 193055 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dear Little Irish Mother, 1927; 193054 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dear Little Isle I Love, The, 1943; 193053 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dear Little Shamrock, 1908, nd; 193052 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dear Old County Mayo, 1909; 193051 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dear Old Donegal, 1942; 193050 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Dear Old Emerald Shore, The, 1880; 193049 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dear Old Fashioned Irish Songs My Mother Sang to Me, 1915; 193048 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Dear Ould Dart, The, 1939; 193047 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Defender of Erin, Ye Fought Not in Vain, 1921; 193046 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Dennis O'Shane, 1868; 193045 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Denny Grady's Hack, 1886; 193044 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Denny Murphy's Daughter Nell, 1896; 193043 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Did Anyone Ever Tell You, Mrs. Murphy, 1949; 193042 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Did Your Mother Come From Ireland, 1931, 1935, 1936; 193041 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dinny Danny, 1921; 193040 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dinty McGinty, 1942; 193039 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Do You Know A Man Named Donohue?, 1912; 193038 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Dolly O'Mally, 1905; 193037 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Donegal Bay, 1914; 193036 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Donegan, 1930; 193035 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Don't Do Dooley, 1902; 193034 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Don't Try to Knock a Chip from Riley's Shoulder, 1896; 193033 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Dooley's Alibi, 1902; 193032 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Doonaree, 1955; 193031 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Doreen, 1916; 193030 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Dorine of Dublin, 1915; 193029 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Dougherty, 1910; 193028 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Down an Old Irish Lane, 1934; 193027 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Down by the Glenside, 1947; 193026 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Down By the River Lee, 1946; 193025 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Down Deep in an Irishman's Heart, 1925; 193024 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Down in the Old Neighborhood, 1926; 565206 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Down Limerick Way, 1919; 193023 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Down Went McGinty, 1942; 193022 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Drill, Ye Tarriers, Drill!, 1888; 193021 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Drink of this Cup, undated; 193020 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Dublin and Belfast United, 1947; 193019 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Dublin Bay, 1912; 193018 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Dublin City, 1948; 193017 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Dublin Daisies, 1909; 193016 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Dublin Devils, 1936; 193015 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Dublin Jig, The, 1951; 193014 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Dublin Mary Brown, 1916; 193013 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Dublin Mary Jane, Dublin Rag, The, Dublin Rag, The, 1889; 193012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Duffy, the Swell, 1884; 193011 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Duna, 1914; 193010 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Dundreary O'Donnell, 1877; 193009 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - E, 336038
    - Eileen, 1917; 193008 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Eileen (2), 1911-1914; 193007 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Eileen Allanna, 1873; 193006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Eileen-Alanna Astore, 1917, nd; 193005 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Eileen O'Dwyer, undated; 193004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Eileen Oge, 1903; 193003 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Eilleen's Answer, 1876; 193002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Eily Riley, undated; 193001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ellen of Lismore, undated; 193000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Ellen O'Hagan, 1904; 192999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Emblems of Ireland, 1914; 192998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Emerald, 1904; 192997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Emerald Isle, The, 1840; 192996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Emerald Isle, The (2), 1901; 336086 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Emerald March Medley of Irish Airs, The, 336087 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Emigrant's Letter, The, undated; 192995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - En-cy-clo-pe-dia McFlinn, 1885; 192994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Enniscorthy, undated; 192993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Erin, 1907, 1919; 192992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Erin Go Brah, undated; 192991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Erin is my Home, undated; 192990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Erin Lover, The, 1906; 192989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Erin the tear and the smile in thine eyes, undated; 192988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Erin Weeps Forsaken, 1852; 192987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Erin, a lament, 1917; 192986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Erin, You're Wearin' A Wonderful Smile, 1922; 192985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Erin=Sweet Isle of the Sea, 1913; 192984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Erin's Isle and You, 1914; 192983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Esmeralda McCann, 1904; 192982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Eveleens Bower, 1817; 192981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Every Little Dog Must Have His Day, 1902; 192980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Every Mother's Son There, Sang, The Wearin' of the Green, 1908; 192979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Every Road Leads Back to Ireland, 1936; 192978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Every Star Falls In Love With It's Mate, 1907; 192977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Every Tear is a Smile in an Irishman's Heart, 1919; 192976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Everybody Loves a Little Bit of Irish, 1915; 192975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Everybody Loves An Irish Song, 1916; 192974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Everything About You Tells Me That You're Irish, 1920; 192973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Exile, The, 1886; 192972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Extra, Extra!, 1885; 192971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Eyes of Irish Blue, 1909; 192970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Eyes of Irish Blue, The, 1913; 192969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - F, 336037
    - Fair Day To-Morrah!, 1948; 192968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Family Overhead, The, 1883; 192967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Fancy Nancy Clancy, 1923; 192966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Fanny O'Donovan's Dance, 1894; 192965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Far Away Ireland, 1986; 192964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Farewell Mavourneen, 1907; 192963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Father in Heaven Bless Mother O'Me, 1917; 192962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Father Matthew, 1878; 192961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Father O'Flynn, undated; 192960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Father Phil, 1895; 192959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Father's a Drunkard and Mother is Dead, 1868; 192958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Faugh-A-Ballagh, Feis Eireann, 1917; 192957 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Fenian Days, 1909; 192956 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Fenian Exiles' Farewell Song, The, 1869; 192955 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Fenians Evermore, 1866; 192954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Fiddler of Dooney, The, 1934; 192953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Fine Ould Irish Gentleman, The, 1845, 1860; 192952 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Finnegan Gave It to Me, 1912; 192951 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Finnegins, The, 1866; 192950 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Finnigan's Irish Band, 1908; 192949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Flower of Erin, 1913; 192948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - For Freedom and Ireland, 1900; 192947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - For Ireland and You, 1915; 192946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - For Killarney and You, 1910; 192945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Forlorn Old Maid, The, 1881; 192944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - For Sadness Can't Dwell, 1919; 192943 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - For the Green, 1903; 192942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - For the Wearing of the Green, 1912; 192941 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Forgive But Don't Forget, 1877; 192940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Four-leaf'd Shamrock, The, 1922; 192939 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - French Taught in Ireland, 1888; 192938 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Full Moon Union, The, 1880; 192937 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - G, 336036
    - Gallagher, 1910; 192936 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Galway Bay, 1947; 192935 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Garden Where the Praties Grow, The, 1929; 192934 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Gay Gosson, The, 1909; 192933 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Gems from the Emerald Isle, undated; 192932 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Gems of Erin, Gems of the Emerald Isle, undated; 192931 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - General Hooligan, Genial Irish Collection, The, 1915; 192930 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Ghost of Kelly, The, 1910; 192929 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Gilligan's On a Tear Again, 1890; 192928 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Girl of a Shantyman's Dream, 1938; 192927 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Girl with a Brogue, The, 1909; 192926 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Give Me a Honeymoon that's Irish, 1910; 192925 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Give Me a Little Bit More Than You Gave Reilly, 1917; 192924 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Give Old Ireland to the Irish, 1921; 192923 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Go Find a Sweetheart from the Emerald Isle, 1908; 192922 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Go Over the Top with Reilly, 1918; 192921 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Golden Jubilee, The, 1941; 192920 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - "Gone Again" Corrigan, 1938; 192919 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Good Old Irish Gentleman, The, 1840; 192918 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Goodbye, Mother Machree, 1918; 192917 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Grandma's Shamrocks, 1898; 192916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Green Fields in Ireland, undated; 192915 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Green Glens of Antrim, The, 1951; 192914 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Green Hills of Old Erin, The, 1883; 192913 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Gypsy Love Song, 1898; 192912 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - H, 336035
    - Half-way to Ireland, 1950; 192911 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hang the Mulligan Banner Up, 1880; 192910 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Hannah Dooley, 1905; 192909 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Happy Hooligan, 1902; 192908 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Harp that Once Thro' Tara's Halls, 1851; 192907 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Harrigan, 1907; 192906 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Has Anybody Here Seen Kelly?, 1909; 192905 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Has Sorrow Thy Young Days Shaded, undated; 192904 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Hat My Father Wore Upon St. Patrick's Day, The, 1909; 192903 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Hat My Father Wore!, The, 1942; 192902 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Haunted Spring, The, undated; 192901 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Have a Jolly Time, 1898; 192900 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Have You Seen Maggie Riley, 1904; 192899 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - He Is Irish, 1891; 192898 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - He Married Riley's Bride, 1895; 192897 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - He Never Deserted a Friend, 1889; 192896 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Heart of My Irish Rose, The, 1933; 192895 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Hello, Patsy Fagan, 1947; 192894 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Her Danny, 1919; 192893 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Her Name is Mary Donohue, 1909; 192892 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - He's Living the Life of Riley, 1917; 192891 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - He's My Boy, 1918; 192890 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Hills of Donegal, The, 1914; 192889 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Hills of Kerry, The, 1909; 192888 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Hippity Hop, 1919; 192887 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - His Name Is Patrick Brannigan, 1891; 192886 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Ho-Ho-Ho-Hogan, 1928; 192885 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Home of Killarney and You, The, 1916; 192884 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Home of the Celt and the Gael, The, 1907; 192883 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Home Rule for Old Ireland, 1878; 192882 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Home to You, Ireland, 1916; 192881 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Honorah, 1906; 192880 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hooligans are Hooli Hooli Mad, The, 1917; 192879 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Hooligan's Fancy Dress Ball, undated; 192878 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Host of the Air, The, 1908; 192877 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - How Are Things in Glocca Morra, 1946; 192876 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - How Can They Tell That Oi'm Irish, 1898; 192875 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - How Can You Buy Killarney, 1948; 192874 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - How Happy Old Ireland Would Be, 1919; 192873 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - How I Got Even with O'Grady, 1888; 192872 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Hush, my Darlings, do not Weep, 1880; 192871 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Hush-a-bye, Ma Baby, 1914; 192870 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Hush-a-bye, Wee Rose of Killarney, 1947; 192869 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Husheen, 1897; 192868 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - I, 336034
    - I am Dreaming of My Irish Rose, 1914; 192867 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - I Didn't Mean to Hurt Your Feeling, I Didn't Mean to Make You Cry, 1909; 192866 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - I Don't Have to Go Back to Ireland, 1950; 192865 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - I Dunno, 1886; 192864 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - I Got a Letter From Ireland, 1916; 192863 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - I Had $15 in my Inside pocket, 1885; 192862 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - I Have a Bonnet Trimmed with Blue, 1963; 192861 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - I Have Loved Her Since I Heard Her Sing Killarney, 1912; 192860 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - I Heard a Piper Piping, 1922; 192859 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - I Know An Irish Garden, 1938; 192858 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - I Know What Love Is, 1870; 192857 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - I Long for the Green Isle of Erin, 1923; 192856 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - I Looked at Norah, 1950; 192855 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - I Lost My Heart in Ireland, 1918; 192854 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - I Love and Adore But Thee, 1917; 192853 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - I Love the Name of Erin, 1913; 192852 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - I Love the Name of Killarney, 1919; 192851 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - I Love the Name of Mary, 1910; 192850 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - I Love to Hear an Irish Band Upon St. Patrick's Day, 1912; 192849 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - I Love You as the Angels Love Killarney, 1915; 192848 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - I Love You Mary, My Irish Fairy, 1915; 192847 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - I Never Met a Girl Like You, 1923; 192846 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - I Never Met Before a Girl Like You, 1913; 192845 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - I Want a Girlie from the Emerald Isle, 1913; 192844 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - I Want an Irish Rose, 1911; 192843 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - I Was Dreaming That Ireland Was Free, 1920; 192842 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - I Wish That I Was Back in Old Killarney, 1912; 192841 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - I Wonder if the Same Moon Shines in Ireland To-Night, 1919; 192840 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - I Wonder Why They Don't Set Ireland Free, 1919; 192839 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - I'd Just Paint the Leaf of the Shamrock, 1920; 192838 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Idol of Erin, The, 1917, 1923; 192837 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - If I Knew That Ireland Was Free, 1919; 192836 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - If I Knock the 'L' Out of Kelly, 1916; 192835 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - If it Wasn't for the Irish and the Jews, 1912; 192834 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - If the Irish Should Win their Grand Liberty, 1920; 192833 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - If They'd Only Give Old Ireland to the Irish, 1919; 192832 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - If They'd Only Move Old Ireland Over Here, 1913; 192831 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - If We Only Had A Robert Emmet Now, 1902; 192830 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - If You Ever Go To Ireland, 1944; 192829 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - If You're Irish, Come Into the Parlor, 1919; 192828 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - If You're Irish, You'll Remember, 1916; 192827 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - I'll Always Be Irish, 1966; 192826 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - I'll Be Back in Dear Old Dublin the Day that Ireland's Free, 1920; 192825 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - I'll Be With You When It's Daisy Time in Dublin, 1916; 192824 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - I'll Buy the Blarney Castle, 1920; 192823 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - I'll Never Have Another Pal Like Mary Mine, 1911; 192822 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - I'll Paralyze the Man that says McGinty, 1890; 192821 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen / Kathleen Mavourneen, 1932, 1942; 192820 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - I'll Tell Me Ma, 1963; 192819 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - I'll Wear the Trowsers, Oh!, 1880; 192818 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - I'm A Long Way From Tipperary, 1914; 192817 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - I'm Awfully Glad I'm Irish, 1910; 192816 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - I'm Crazy 'Bout Somebody, 1912; 192815 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - I'm Doublin' Back to Dublin, 1920; 192814 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - I'm Going Back to Erin, 1915; 192813 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - I'm Going Back to Old Erin, 1915; 192812 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - I'm Going Back to Those I Love in Ireland, 1916; 192811 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - I'm Hearin' from Erin, 1917; 192810 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - I'm Irish, 1889; 192809 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - I'm Longing For My Little Irish Home, 1911; 192808 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - I'm Looking Over a Four Leaf Clover, 1927; 192807 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - I'm Not Myself At All, undated; 192806 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - I'm Off to Kelly's Isle, undated; 192805 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - I'm On Agen with Monaghan, 1910; 192804 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - I'm on My Way to Dublin Bay, 1905, 1915; 192803 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - I'm Such a Naughty Kid, 1894; 192802 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - I'm Tickled to Death That You're Irish, 1919; 192801 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - In A Doorway in Galway, 1940; 192800 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - In An Irish Jaunting Car, 1920; 192799 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - In County Clare, 1921; 192798 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - In Dear Old Ireland, 1912; 192797 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - In Dreams I Return to the Green Hills of Erin, 1918; 192796 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - In Ireland, 1905; 192795 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - In My Wild Mountain Valley, undated; 192794 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - In Old Ireland Meet Me There, 1903, 1912; 192793 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - In Old Ireland That's Just Where I Long To Be, 1913; 192792 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - In Old Ireland where the River Kenmare Flows, 1911; 192791 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - In the Beautiful Vale Where the Blackwater Flows, 1913; 192790 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - In the Dark, 1905; 192789 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - In the Good Old Irish Way, 1907; 192788 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - In the Heart of an Irish Rose, 1916; 192787 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - In the Hills of Killarney, 1916; 192786 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - In the Hills of Old Killarney, 1915; 192785 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - In the Land Where the Shamrock Grows, 1910; 192784 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - In the Land Where the Shamrock Grows (2), 1919; 192783 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - In the Land Where the Shamrock Grows (3) / Dear Heart, 1919; 565207 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - In the Vales of Killarney, undated; 192782 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - In the Valley Where My Sally Said Good-Bye, 1907; 192781 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Independence Day in Dublin Town, 1914; 192780 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Ireland, 1915; 192779 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ireland (2), 1915; 192778 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ireland (3), 1912; 192777 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Ireland A! Gra Ma Chree, Ireland Calling, 1901; 192776 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Ireland Dear Ireland, 1914; 192775 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Ireland I Hear You Calling, 1915; 192774 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Ireland Is Calling, 1917; 192773 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Ireland is Ireland to Me, 1915; 192772 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Ireland Is Your Home Sweet Home, 1917; 192771 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Ireland Isn't Ireland Anymore, 1909; 192770 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Ireland Must Be A Garden, 1923; 192769 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Ireland Must Be Free, 1921; 192768 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Ireland Must Be Heaven For My Mother Came From There, 1916; 192767 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ireland my Ireland, 1917; 192766 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ireland my Ireland (2), 1918; 192765 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ireland Never Seemed So Far Away, 1912; 192764 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ireland Sweet Land Across the Sea, 1915; 192763 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ireland Will Be Happy Ireland Again, 1885; 192762 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Ireland Won Her Freedom, 1917; 192761 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Ireland, Dear, My Heart's For You, 1917; 192759 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ireland, I Love You, Acushla Machree!, 1900-1910; 192758 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Ireland, Ireland, 1903; 192757 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Ireland, My Land of Dreams, 1918; 192756 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Ireland, My Sireland, 1917; 192755 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Ireland, the Footstool of God, 1916; 192754 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Ireland, We Sympathize With You, 1919; 192753 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Ireland's Appeal, 1888; 192752 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Ireland's Freedom, 1880; 192751 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Ireland's Loss Was Heaven's Gain, 1917; 192750 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Ireland's Native Green, 1886; 192749 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Irish, The, 1903; 192748 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Irish American Athletic Club March, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Irish Beauties, 1911; 192747 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Irish Blues, The, 1915; 192746 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Irish Christening, The, 1877; 192745 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Irish Colonel, The, 1913; 192744 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Irish Cradle Song, 1951; 192743 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Irish Cradle Song (2), 1897; 192742 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Irish Discovery, The, 1894; 192741 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Irish Eyes, 1912; 192740 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Irish Eyes (2), 1927; 192739 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Irish Eyes of Love, 1914; 192738 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Irish Fancy, 1956; 192737 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - An Irish Folk Song, 1894, 1922; 192736 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Irish Fox Trot, The, 1908; 192735 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Irish Have a Great Day To-night, The, 1917; 192734 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Irish Hearts, 1906; 192733 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Irish in Me, The, 1958; 192732 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Irish Jubilee, The, 1890; 192731 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Irish Jug, 1963; 192730 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Irish Kaiser, The, 1917; 192729 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Irish Lads in Blue, The, 1901; 192728 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Irish Lullaby, 1914; 192727 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Irish Ma O'Mine, 1915; 192726 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Irish Mambo, 1954; 192725 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Irish Moon, 1923; 192724 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Irish Mother's Lament, The, undated; 192723 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Irish Names, 1908; 192722 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Irish Patrol, 1881; 192721 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Irish Piper, The, 1893; 192720 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Irish Pipers, 1935; 192719 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Irish Potheen, 1882; 192718 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Irish Rag, 1910; 192717 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Irish Republic, The, 1895, 1926; 192716 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Irish Schoolmaster, The, undated; 192715 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Irish Serenade, 1894; 192714 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Irish Soldier Boy, The, Irish Songs, Vol. II, 1950; 192713 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Irish Spinning Song, 1894; 192712 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Irish Sport, The, 1892; 192711 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Irish Spree, The, undated; 192710 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Irish Steeple Chase, The, undated; 192709 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Irish Tango, The, 1914; 192708 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Irish Tavern, The, 1895; 192707 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Irish Tune from County Derry, 1911, 1939; 192706 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Irish Volunteers, The, 1904, 1917; 192705 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Irish Walk, The, 1903; 192704 (Box 19, Folder 9)